okay well until people can respect my rules I mean it's like I it's not whatever
you guys want to talk about that yeah you're both you're both breaking the
rules like you know just because one person breaks them you should break
them it's not gonna all it doesn't hurt my channel it doesn't help it doesn't help
me it's not interesting it's not funny doesn't yeah
so
As long as you're gonna be doing that stuff, I can't have you on the show
I mean, I'd love to have you on the show
If you can like talk nicely, but you guys just keep
People accusing form bombing or doxing as like why do you keep doing it?
I asked you not to do it the first time you're just gonna fight you. Let's do it on your own show
I'm just trying to I'm just trying to have
I know flirty, but it's like, you know, you're putting that photo up of her kissing Christine and she puts the other way
It's like it's not nothing I'm having to do with it. You know, just don't don't put the photos up
She won't put a photo up. We're all happy, but you keep putting it up
But yeah, I don't know if you have
You know, I know I don't know you guys are just keep going at it
Like I don't it's just gonna hurt my channel because your eyes are gonna stick or striking my channel
But I have already deleted it
Yeah, so maybe I have to have you one at a time and maybe I just can't have you all together because you're to keep
Yeah, Tiffany, it's not easy, right? It's like everyone keeps yeah
Yeah, I just say just don't just normally put a photo up and that's gonna be that'd be the end of it
But it's like everyone has you guys keep putting photos up. I
Just stand one person that I don't see who does it first or I don't really care
It's not it's not anything that's gonna affect you the person. I'll just all we'll do is is
Yeah
Okay, I don't know. I just know I can't have two for chat. Yeah. Yeah, this is too much
Because I just like I keep saying don't stop doing it. I'm just gonna keep having to end the stream
You're like, oh, she's porn bombing. You know, I don't I don't see poor bombing
I don't know but 40 diamond keeps standing up. That was the thumbnail of the video a story diamond standing up with with the fake peanut
I mean a second. So I mean, I don't think that even if it's like, okay, I don't think it's like
Appropriate for you. So I just hadn't
So for three diamond like you have to stop putting the summer picture up
You have to stop standing up with that thing in your pants and summer
She does that and please don't put a photo up either, but otherwise I can't it's just like I can't keep ending the streams
And I know you're not porn bombing, but it's like then
So people will cues right not really believing I just like say I can't see I got there was like
I've got a beefy alley bomb like I've been bombed with like somebody where can see like this little nipples showing
It's that basically people just try to like
You know just like you know
Put it on the I don't know. I don't know people working through we're gonna she showed your balls
Well, it's okay. Like just guys. I'm not sure if there's balls. It's not the place to do that, you know
you want to show each other's balls you know we can like they can like schedule a trip and
you know we can do like what the locker room or something like that i don't know it's not not on
the show i mean i don't know i i don't want to see any more balls i want to see balls i can go to
pornhub i can see i can see many balls i want i want to see 40 diamonds balls or any pictures i don't
Yeah, Jamie join you. How about Jamie? I know I know but what we're back and forth. I can't have Alice was too much
Yeah, buy a super chat guys you want to you want to show balls let's just support to the channel
Ali Alejandro, Ali Alejandro, my ours is by Ali Alejandro, I love Alex.
He's nice. That's sweet.
Okay guys. What up?
Okay guys, please no photos. Thank you. I did not show any photos since you did.
Yeah you are. You showed photos first.
My second you stop the bullshit. That's how this works. You do the bullshit. I'm gonna bring the bullshit
Shut the fuck up dimples calm down
Both of you have your own panels to do this bullshit on, to bring to psychics is really good.
Alex shut the fuck up, I'm not talking to you.
But you say that all the time.
Shut the fuck up.
You say that all the time.
Go fight someone else.
He doesn't like it.
You know what, when you get over here, so what's the difference?
Alex, you literally threatened to...
Go take your little grievance, but you literally threatened to RAP me.
No, if you can do it here, I can do it here. Don't fuck yourself.
You threatened to RAP me on PsychoSpanish, so you have no right to talk about nothing.
I didn't try and shit, fat boy.
I literally have a video of you threatening to RAP me.
It's fucking sweet.
I have a video of you threatening to RAP me.
Shut the fuck up, and I'll go to your channel talk to you about that, but psyche doesn't want to do RAP me on psyche's channel
No, no one is
This is not good for shit and come on
Yeah, let's let's all come down
Alice is a voice of reasons
I
Like I made you break TOS on your life, you know many times
You know, he's not the voice of reason psyche, you know, don't make me a diamond fucking agree right now, okay?
Come on Alex, I know you're gonna take it from me. You're fucking and I see I'm loving it
I love hearing you to go at it right now, but psyching in the back room like stop
Alex, you have nothing you have no right to talk about nothing after you fucking threaten to fucking grape me
You can't even talk
Mexicali gangster you threaten to grape me on psyching something panel
Prove yes, you did psych he has been sent the fucking videos. I'd be like, you're full of shit. Shut up
He's been sent out. I'll take it out. I'll divert multiple people have seen you fucking threatened to fucking
RAP me on
Dime doesn't care about himself. He doesn't care about nobody.
I understand that. I know you didn't like her.
Like the transsexual vampire from hell.
Do you want the clip somewhere? Do you want the clip somewhere?
No, I didn't.
I didn't know it was the clip.
He didn't like her.
She admitted it though. She said it herself.
Oh well, but don't use her as a scapegoat because you're fucking treating her like shit right now.
I'm not doing nothing to her.
I haven't spoken to her since the 24th.
The 24th you put on the calendar you write it down. No, I have good memories
To deliver plasma you wanted quick money because you're so broke. No one fuck your fat ass
I want to do something good.
I'm going to do something good for my mother.
And they were like, get out of here trying to freak.
That's insane.
No, that's not what I said.
No, I said they needed a doctor signature.
I gave back the 23.
I love trying to get a signature for my doctor.
They say you need a signature for my doctor.
That's all they need.
Go to see mother
And you're a fucking weird ass fucking you're weird. Yeah, you're a great per
I didn't go so blood for fucking weed money. You threatened to grape me you fucking
I'm in you time me out, bitch
See psyche you take my wrench away and this bitch is playing games. I'm not a mod
Well, why is it saying right now?
Has failed to pose to fly and I'm not trying to post the flirty diamond I'm posting no I am not a mod
I can tell him what it's saying in red. Okay. What does it say? It says
This comment has failed to post to flirty diamond. I'm not doing it. It's a flirty diamond. I'm talking to fucking
Streaming so it says it didn't go under her chat. You're coming. It's just going into my chat
Before what they started with that
Yeah, what is it when people start re-streaming and then you cannot then they did the comments they put
We'll go to both go over both channels sometimes, but sometimes it I
Never fucking banded you from my channel for well apparently I'm bland in your channel. No, you're not
I never been I don't bend no one for my channel summer
I don't bend no one from my channel. I'll take the screen shot and send it to psyche and he could show you
Zach, oh, I don't have discord
So I post it again it might post her channel it might have been like a temporary thing why can't I don't ban no one from my channel
I wouldn't let me give me a second. I'll just do it again. Just no point to me
There's no bad man people for my channel first of all everyone matters. So all lives matter. Why Ben? Why Ben?
I'm gonna put in this like
I'm switching the picture
So I could show you what it says, but diamond still has you and Christine kissing on her post. No, I
Did you do? Yes, you did.
Yeah, that A.I. shit.
That doesn't matter. I don't have a tag.
That doesn't matter.
I can't see that shit.
That's just a photo of your fucking...
Now.
I don't know why it says that, actually.
I don't know why it says that because
I don't have you banned.
Make screamy, S.I.K.E.
I already read it.
See, I don't know why it says that actually
You guys in high school. This is a high school girls act
I
Don't
Like I'm not fucking
Maybe it's on your blog. I don't know people
I post it on my backup account. I'm not stupid enough to post shit on my fucking main channel
Know
Yeah, I have a conversation. Yeah, I'm a nice conversation. I got more
Nobody cares about what you're saying. I care. This is between summer and night. You have nothing to do with this
So go to your own panel fight about it. I want to talk to psyche
I know there's a million people that want to come up here right now and talk to psyche
So I can tell us to come up. So yeah, like what the hell
Look, I don't have you tagged on nothing watch your camera off
My camera I'm in the dark. I'm out. No you're you got fingerprints on it
don't have you tagged on nothing well you see what it said I don't know why it
says I somewhere I'm not lying I don't know why I'm I never seen that myself
either that's the first time that I've ever seen something in that I don't have
you talk on nothing dude
don't have you tagged what's the point of having a video of us up like for
because Christine case looking talking shit to me what does it mean I missed
it what video I missed it there's a video what is it I don't know I'm not
gonna make another video I should have been it you're not and she put up a
video of you and Christine that was like months ago
Yeah, and then you took it down and put it back up cuz it's fucking stupid
Everybody telling you Christine ever even called you a predator and yeah
I said, you know what maybe she deleted her comment
Now now you didn't I said maybe she deleted her comment that's all I said
What is the random bullshit?
What is the random ass shit, psyche?
Okay, that's why I'm getting mad.
At first I was laughing, but now I'm mad.
Yeah, like psyche psyche is not supposed to have music actually
So I don't in the world's not supposed to have people with a dick and tits and all crazy either
Alex you're fucking annoying. You're annoying. You came up here for what to annoy you
Cuz I'm annoying. Thank you. Thank you
Yeah, there we go, that was cute
I mean, I appreciate her coming up here, but now I'm just like
Say sake we were trying to have an actual conversation and like
This bitch is crazy
Like you're annoying you're annoying us. I mean actually I'm not gonna speak for summer. So never mind. You're annoying me. I
Do not have you tagged on anything and I don't want to make a whole video about Christine
Like I am okay well as long as I'm up and on this shit, then it's I mean
You want me to make a beat about Christine no really don't you really should just leave this shit alone
But you know what I mean your beef will go to me alone cuz I've been leaving her alone
And she won't fucking leave me alone
No, I mean you poke and then when she gets started then you're like no no
I never said nothing to her. I never said nothing to her
Girl you always play the victim you always know I said nothing to Christine actually I never say anything to Christine
There's that I told Christine to fuck off actually
Okay, so then you tell it's up the dirt
Yeah, cuz she kept fucking talking about me
well
When somebody talks about her she talks about them I didn't talk about her until she started talking about me
girl
I didn't I didn't fucking talk about her until she
Everything right and I don't care. I didn't start talking about her
See everything like it's I was in the chat and minding my fucking business and then Christine started attacking me
Oh, I know because everyone attacks you she did. I was
On panel minding my business talking to fucking spunk
Video
Because you were just part of that video two months ago. Yeah, well, then I guess I'm just gonna keep on I guess we're just gonna keep on doing the stupid
Okay, you can keep on
Two months ago you took it out two months ago, and we'll keep arguing then
We'll keep arguing because I'm not gonna take down a video until she stops talking about me. Yeah
Your fuck I like we got it. You're fucking with us. Yeah. Well, are they enough man? Look at these beautiful couple
I'll get a fuck a room and fuck each other. Whoa
Why?
How come there's no audio?
Cuz they got this in the land. Is that US or is that like a vacation?
Yeah, they're cute couple, but take the temper down, baby
Are you okay? Where are you for you? I don't see your camera. I'm accepting a cash up right now from
I'm gonna catch up one second. Okay
Very weird. Yeah, well
This is kind of like the guy from a little sasco from man TV and then Nicole still
I mean, you know, I guess that's okay. So I comment on her man
I
I'm not
Said I told you from day one
To put any videos of you. Why don't y'all just yeah, but she keeps talking about she keeps talking to me in the comments
No, I'm above that
No, I'm above
Throw our video up
go away go away your brains gonna reset Alex
What are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over? No, I'm no one cares
Like you no one
Like this is not gonna fix anything
I
Okay, well, I don't care that he got backstage
But I'm just saying like and talk her scene stop talking about me like I told you from the start
Leave me alone
I never
Everybody always
Talking to her I told her to leave me the fuck alone
I literally said fuck off I want that videos up. I'll tell you that right now. I said K
Why I don't give a fuck about the video cuz I was annoying me
So I don't give a fuck she ain't gonna she's not gonna stop until like the video comes down that video comes down
She might pop
She needs to leave me alone already
He was talking shit to me before I upload that video
I'm just letting you know you want her to stop talking shit about you. Well, you have that video up
Kept talking shit to me before I had a video up
Listen on private of the video. She kept talking shit diamond in your fucking fit of yours and your boyfriend's fucking little
Whatever fighting everybody
You don't think maybe there was some fucking
I have no control of him. He is not
I'm not talking about him. Listen to what i'm saying in your all's adventure of all of that
Okay, you're already with all kinds of fucking people
So you may have said something and not fucking remembered it. I never said
If you want her to back the fuck off take the video down
I could eat great pussy. I don't care. I do not fucking condone with fucking raging sass to people. I don't condone it
That's not what i'm talking about. You're not listening to me
Like I don't you think I support him telling people are fucking about his check about child children and all this
I don't condone that I don't like that shit. You think that I like him talking about fucking people
You stupid bitches. Shut up. Both of you need to get slapped in the face with them dick. Shut the fuck up.
What are you both on crack? It's broken by the video. If it wasn't there, she wouldn't come at you.
Well, I did the video. Well, if it wasn't there, for two hours straight. Both of you need to shut the fuck up and go suck a dick, whatever.
You fucking let's get the fuck out of you that shit enough
You're a guy
So this is a mental issue my friends we
Whatever, yeah, so I'm a mental to me. So summer is a grandmother pretending
like she's 10 years old to fight in high school, fighting some fight.
And they say, oh, I'm actually, I would like me to pretend it's about Alex.
What does that say about you, Alex? You tend to great need this by being trans.
He's so loud. I mean, he's just so loud because he trances mic all the way up.
It's like, you know, he does very screaming about, you know,
he trances his whole mic up every single time he goes on here.
We're having a nice conversation, we're having a nice conversation, a nice conversation.
Look, I have no, I am never condoned.
Raging telling talking talking about their children
People this is the point I'm making you you you know y'all were on y'all's little whatever escapade y'all wouldn't fight me each other
Well, but all this weird shit says him and I talk about nature and I talk privately already about me sharing his news
And I fucking apologize to him and he forgave me
Why do you think I saw watching movies with him because of it?
Why do you think I fucking took away his privileges? I guess his privilege
I mean if you want to be if you want me to talk about it what privileges did you take away because I don't
Watch I don't allow him to watch movies with me anymore. I told him once he cuts his shit
I will start watching movies with him again. It pisses me off
I don't want this stupid drama that he's fucking causing. It's pissing me off
It's annoying me to the fucking max. So you want to hold him accountable. Okay, Harding. Hear me out
You want to hold him accountable, right? You want to sit there and say, you know what?
I don't want this shit anymore. All this is stupid and needs to stop
But yet you won't let your ego go and just see if you take that video down if Christina stop
And then that that's one less fucking headache. You got to worry about
And as I said once she stops I will find
But she's not going to as long as that video's up
Well, she should be true gooder
She said that she didn't, she said she wouldn't mind kissing you though. She said she wouldn't mind kissing you
I'm not an ugly bitch. Don't act like I'm ugly.
I never said you were ugly. I said you were old, not ugly.
I'm not old either, Diamond. 46 is not fucking old, bitch.
Okay, but you have like 22 years on me.
So what? You can learn some shit from me, bitch.
Okay? Well, I never sa-
This is unnecessary shit out of everyone in this community, like real shit out of everyone in this community, me and you, I mean, I've done what you're doing. You feel me? Like this is where this is the dumbest shit we should be fighting.
You know what you guys said about reading is that he was taking advantage of me. You know that right?
You guys taking advantage of me my point. Okay. First of all, I didn't even know you and Rachel were talking
This is some real shit, and you know, I've been busy. I haven't been around you guys said yesterday on your live
That he was taking advantage of me
He is taking advantage of you.
No, he's not.
Yes, he is.
You don't see that right now.
How is he taking advantage of me?
How is he?
Do you want me to be honest?
Don't interrupt me, Diamond.
And I'm being genuinely real with you right now.
When I sit there and Kate showed the messages that was between you all, were
you and him or just talking or whatever?
Cause again, I don't know what anything was going on because I haven't been around.
I noticed how he was manipulating you, how he was love bombing you.
Women like us have been through a lot of things.
The one thing we want the most is somebody is going to see us for us.
When somebody is manipulating you and gaslighting you and love bombing you,
and then in the midst of all that,
he says to you, I just love the way you make Bita so mad.
Maybe he's playing with your head.
And I'm being for real right now at first. I was upset because I didn't understand what was going on
But then now I'm upset because it's and then he even did it
Remember the night you two were on panel and I came up here, right?
And then you two left he even try to he tries to do it even with me because he knows that me and Bedar are cool, right?
He goes summer. I love you summer. I'm gonna be on your panel summer. I love you. You don't know me
Okay, love me. I mean, yeah, he's came over to my shit a couple times. Well, come on dude, really?
He said he loved you because he wanted to fucking keep the peace. That's all why he said that and he
He says that all the time, but that's that's not even the point the point was I know
But I'm just saying the text messages between you two
You may not see it right now diamond and I don't expect you to but I'm letting you know from a og
Maybe you getting played
And if I was being played, why would he be on the phone with me all day every day watching these sweetie?
That's a part of that's too time-consuming. Do you okay? First of all, do you know what narcissists does not be?
I already have a fucking scar on my fucking eyebrow because of that shit. Okay, so
This is what I'm gonna try to and I'm not saying this in a disrespect way. I really am not try to think about this in a
Not so emotional way because right now it's emotional for you and I get that I understand that
But narcissists to people. What do they do? They're gonna build you up and
Then for whatever it is they need you to do
Everybody knows and even since I've entered this community
He is fucking hurt by whatever him and Bita had going on and I still don't know and it's not my business
But it's very clear that this man has been very scorned by her. Okay, you think it's all of a sudden
You think that he just thinks you got a cool brain and you know how to pick good movies
that now all of a sudden he's, you know what I mean?
Spending the time and talking to you.
You're gonna talk about this movie, so we talk about life.
You're gonna talk about everything.
You're gonna talk about his darkest, deepest times,
his heartbreaks, his things that happened to him as a child,
what he wants to do, what he sees in you,
how he thinks you can be amazing.
That's, baby, it's a part of the game.
And you're in the game, and you know this,
but sometimes there might be somebody
that sparks that nerve with us just a little bit.
Because again diamond, I'm looking at you and telling you I understand what it's like to all you want is somebody to see you as a real person I
Get it
I'm not bullshitting you right now my whole life. I've been treated like a piece of me like
100%
Because that's what I do in life. I get what I do in life. Yes, I make videos where yes
I target an audience to just treat me like a piece of meat
I know what I'm doing on on social media to promote myself, right, but I don't
We don't even he's taking it he he's taking it
He's making it personal and he's he's getting to that point because like I you know listen
Why would he ask me about my real life if I see and if I'm just being honest, please just hear me out
And understand I'm not talking about me, right? I'm just using this as role-playing right
But if I think somebody if I was if I was if I hadn't been addicted to get somebody and I really wanted to rock a bitch or whatever
It is there was something I wanted done and I didn't want to do it myself
And I came across the body that I seen is very vulnerable that is very you know, I'm saying like
Women like us whether we realize it or not and we don't realize it until later on in life sometimes
And maybe we do, but we just don't realize other people can see it. We want to be loved. We want to be accepted
We want to be seen we want to be heard because we never had that from five years old diamond and all my life
I've never had that my mom and father didn't give a fuck about me
Nobody ever gave a fuck about me, you know what I mean?
And I fell in a lot of bad bad situations because all I wanted to do is be loved
I wanted to be seen I wanted to be respected
I wanted to all that and it never worked out.
It always started out with somebody telling me, you know, what's your dreams?
You can tell me anything.
I got you.
I'm going to share my, you know, whatever, you know, telling you the truth,
or he could be making sure.
When am I DMs, my old pimp was going to fucking traffic me again.
And I want, I mean, yes, I was going to condone.
I was going to allow it, but you know, raging showed me something differently.
I understand that and and nothing I say right now in this moment is gonna make sense to you
Well, yeah, I'm drunk right now. Well, and it even besides that you have an emotional attachment with him right now
Okay, and I am mad at you about that because I understand that process
Not only because I've been through it because of the work that I also do
Only friend that I would start I stayed friends with fucking
Started fucking telling the one person attacking me
That they're doing good by attacking me and the only person to defend me was him
Summer the only person to defend me and that moment was raging
But it that doesn't mean that he was defending you for your purpose
It doesn't it may have felt that way
And whatever, but it doesn't mean necessarily that that's what he was doing
When people have agendas it can make it look real pure it can make it look real honest
Which is being real, but why blow up my phone 24 7
When awake if I know I can get you to do what I need you to do then you know I'm saying and and all I got to do is
Give you attention
And clearly he's got some shit going on too, you know what I mean cuz none of this is you know
I mean you sent me photos with his fucking family
Okay, and I'm not even I'm obviously I'm never gonna fucking do you know, I'm never gonna show those photos
But like why would he show me photos of what with his fuck?
Why would he dox his fucking family for me?
Though like I don't want him when he showed me those photos. I thought to myself
I thought to myself, why the fuck is he doing this for?
Even though...
I need you need to listen to your first go your gut your first unseen and if that was your first unseen you need to
hide in on that
Like he's got it, you know, whatever you got going on. So you're it is not that I didn't
See him in a different in a different way because I never obviously seen him around other people
But to me
He lives in a whole different continent
Right a whole different continent
Why isn't he trying to be with somebody in real life? I
Wonder that
You know me it ain't even just like he lived in Mexico or he was in Canada like he was
He told me he's not gonna interfere interfere with my real love life
If any if I got with anybody in my real life. He would not blame me
And I'm not saying what's happening between him and I isn't real. I'm not saying that
but what I'm just saying if I
If I so happen to somehow fall in love with somebody that's I'm right nearby. He said he wouldn't interview with that
Yes
And this conversation probably went way too far than it needed to on the internet, but at the end of the day, I said what I said, you're not, you know, you're either going to hear it or you'll hear it, fill it later.
But you just need to be.
You need to watch ass and you still own you know, they're still shitty parts on your end that all this, you know
I mean all this and I never said that me sharing his fucking dick pic wasn't wrong to me
That's gonna sit that's revenge porn. I know that's considered revenge porn. I know that yeah 100% it is
And I mean he was pissed off this brand that this and you know, this is what upsets me
You know, you'll you'll be like well summer. There's no you know, you're you're supposed to be an avid first
I'm not an avid for trans trans
But I am an ally and it pisses me off to the core because I know people that have died because of what you're doing and
You think it's a game and so not only when you attack me as a woman
But then when you do shit like that dude like I literally have had people die because of that
And you just I don't like it nobody when I talk to them. I don't lie to anybody
It doesn't matter if you lie to him or not
It's the embarrassing part that you're doing that is going to get you hurt
Well, they can't handle being with a trans person. They shouldn't be fucking with one. Well, you know what?
That's a true, and I know you've been out your whole life. And yes, I know that I know the
You've been out your whole life. Yes, and I know the world shouldn't be so black and white like how I think it is
I I know the world isn't as black and white as how I fucking see it
But in my own head, I personally truly believe at the end of the day
If you can't handle being what a trans person that is out and open about being trans don't fuck with them
Well, whether that's that whether I agree with you or not
That's not the point of what I'm talking about is the fact that you think you can go then when someone trusted you with something
And then shame them with it on a public eye and shame him
Sweetie whether you realize it or not
men, especially straight men or undercover men, whatever, dude, the embarrassment from
that.
Well, he never should have fucked with me if he's so embarrassed, he never should have
fucked with me.
That's fine and dandy, but you're going to pay for that eventually with the wrong one
that comes along.
That's all I'm telling you.
You know how many men I go, I've gone out on dates with in real life, people that are
out here and they are doing everything and all they want to do is fucking live and be
You know how many people go on actual dates with and how many people I just gone to the grocery store in that I lived with before and
That's fine and I need to be engaged summer. I was being gauged. I just be a step mom
I used to be a step mom. Well, I I have been embraced to the fullest extent in life as possible
And no, I never wanted to be a step mom before
Never bad. I was one. I don't think you're ready for all that. That's just my opinion, but
Yeah, cuz it's fucking baby mama's. Oh my god, I'm only gonna get into that right now
But I'm just saying like no
I was talking about all this fit and we like seriously you want the shit between you and Christine to fucking stop
Just take the fuck a video down. It's not that goddamn serious like really it's fine
I just want her to stop fucking saying I lured people off the last one.
Maybe she will if she fucking takes the video down, dude.
You want her to stop.
You want her to sit here and do something when we squash it.
We've been cool.
You've came on my panel and everything.
And then you want to, you, you want her to bow like, come on, man.
It's not that I want her to fucking bow down.
I don't want no one to fucking bow down to me.
I don't believe that.
You ever say you need to stop or I'm not going to take it down.
That doesn't make sense.
Yeah cuz I'm tired of the shit between her and I
And even after we squashed it, and she continued, even after I first took the video down, she continued, and I'm going to continue as long as that is up there.
She kept doing it after.
Because there's no people diamond, it's pointless.
Even when I took the video down, she fucking continued, and continued, and continued.
No she didn't, no she didn't, no she didn't, no she didn't.
Yes she did.
No, that's not all this bullshit started, and this again.
No, she kept attacking me.
Despite me kicking the beat. Yes, she did summer. No, she didn't anyway. Yeah, whatever
I'm just letting you know you want her to stop take the video down if you don't it don't stop. It's cool
We I'm not gonna sit here and stop my shit if you almost keep playing too like I'm gonna keep playing too
And I'm gonna do what I've been doing the last 24 hours. I don't fuck
Thank you for the publicity then
And then see what happens
Yeah, just take it down see what happens video take it down see if it stops and if it stops
Then cool if it don't then put the bitch back up
Yeah, and I did that already
I mean do it again, but it's just a straight over time. I think
Accountability in your actions as well that I've been like seriously. Yeah, I caught her boss implants cuz she started talking about my boobs
She put no video up for you
So be a woman if that's what you're gonna identify us and fucking talk shit to her. She doesn't have a platform
Well, you do you all can argue on this one on my
Psychi's platform
Because you know everybody can tell us it over here
So if she doesn't have a platform that means you're attacking somebody that's just on panels and in chats, you know
And so she's not yeah, well, she needs to leave me alone
But you know
Well, I think summer
All this fucking switch is up and now all the blame is on me
I blame you I'm bringing me in for sure now everything
The whole
What reason does the whole blame is on me now?
We're not talking about raising right now. So now you're drunk crying and whatever I don't care like I don't do shit to no one
Oh, but you do you do?
No, I know
You're gonna keep getting bullshit. I don't do shit to no
Well, you do and now you're drunk crying on fuck a panel. So why don't you jump off panel and so you can pull yourself together?
Fuck.
You don't get to sit there and starts it and the thing that you get to you know
Oh, well, they better stop if you all don't stop then I'm not gonna take it out. Don't take it down
I don't give a shit. I don't start showing no one bitch. I don't start
Yourself cross some orbit cross some orbit
I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck
Don't fucking
This is fun to me bitch
Yeah, you're sick in the head. You're fucking weird.
I am. Crabbit.
You're sick in the head. You're a weird-ass bitch.
You're a weirdo.
You're a weird bitch.
That's what you are. You're weird.
You're weird.
You're a weird-ass fucking bitch.
You're a weird bitch.
Are you emotional?
You're a weird fucking bitch.
I'm a bitch. I am.
I know that I'm that bitch always you're weird you ain't gonna stop me
Cross some more. You're a weird ass fucking bear some more bitch
You're weird
You're weird fuck that's what you are. I'll be weird all day long bitch. You're a crybaby
And you're a weird fucking bitch. You're a weird ass bitch. That's what you are. You're weird
That's why rage is using you bitch
No, he's not yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
You big fucking cry baby cry about that bitch cry about how Bita used to be your friend and you
I don't care about what happened between Bita and I. I don't care about Bita. I don't care about her.
All he's doing is confuse you to try to get her. You know that right?
You think I care about Bita?
You blame as fuck.
And your bitch ass boyfriend is too. Holler.
Nah, he's not my boyfriend.
You know he's watching right? He's watching you cry on panel bitch.
Yeah, you can sell. Yeah. Oh, he's definitely watching you think he's watching
No, he was on the phone with me. He fell asleep on the phone. He's what now he's watching. No, he was nori
He was nori. Yeah, long term. He was nori
Literally what I was talking about in the fall asleep. He fell asleep snoring
grab it
No, you're never gonna make me cry. Yeah, but you already did on video. No
You won't never make me cry.
I just donated a couple of memberships to the chat if anyone wants to.
To donate some tonight. I'll maybe like donate some more, but uh, yeah
Christina's donated a bunch. Hey, there's Miguel. Hey, what's up, Miguel? How are you doing tonight?
If you let him back up, that's the most inappropriate thing to do right now if you let him back up
I probably take you off before you had him
Yeah, I don't think it's appropriate having both of my panel at the same time. No, I don't either. Yeah, yeah
So I I know I know I know about you know
Yeah, so if you just try to come up, I'll probably ask you to step back. Do you wipe your tears off your face bitch?
I'm not crying. You are
No, I was it. No, I wasn't trying to turn your fucking camera off numnets. No, I was drinking more
You were crying bitch. No, I was drinking more actually. Hmm. I started drinking my other beatbox. You dumb bitch
Yeah, okay. I did I was start drinking my other beatbox
I started drinking my other B-Box, that's all.
You're pathetic.
You're pathetic, too.
Bounce.
Well, no, bitch, I got a lot going for me, bitch.
No, you're pathetic.
You came up here to argue with me because you're pathetic.
Like I said, this is gonna be fun. I'm gonna I wonder if I can make you cry every night on panel
You came up here just who are you with me because you're
As soon as I've seen you I knew I was coming up here
Chaser
Never you're a tranny chaser. That's how you came up here because you were chasing a tranny. No, bitch
No, you were chasing a tranny around
All day every day you were chasing a tranny around
That's what you've been doing. You've been chasing a tranny
That's how you do
You've been chasing a tranny somewhere. That's all you do is chase
He wants to try on the panel just now. You know that right you chase trannies
It's sitting there
No, you chase Chinese
Okay on panel. It's okay. You chase Chinese. It's okay. He's using you and you chase Chinese baby
You'll never be number one bitch. You'll always be number two. You're chasing and I'm walking views around and his mind
She's always number one. I don't think I know how people know what makes you think I don't have people on the side
But you emotionally want to be somebody's number one and you can never be
No, I'm not you
I'm not you ain't gonna have to be nobody's number one for baby. I'm not you baby. I'm not you
That's 17 years, baby
17 years bitch. You could
What you finally found a man that's gonna just pain for you
As a wifey with him
Man, give me one fucking monthly allowance to live with. Oh
Well, you're getting bread like a nasty whore now for 17 years for an allowance
Dragon that's what you're doing is getting bread like a filthy ass whore for 17 years
You've been getting
You'll probably be dead before that happens you're getting bred like a filthy ass whore
No, probably be dead before that happens bitch. I'm so proud of you for being bred like a filthy whore for 17 years
I'm so proud of you
Because also you're you doing is getting bred like a filthy whore now and I think it's funny that you'll never be number one bitch
I think it's funny how you literally accepted a tiny little monthly allowance
when you saw it on your dick, you probably wish it was beta.
I'm so sorry that you
Like that he's probably got her picture why he's showing you a dick jerk it off to her and just send in you the picture
I'm so sorry that you literally fell in love with a fucking trick you nasty bitch. No dragon bitch
You fell in love with a trick. I'm very bad for you. Yeah. Well, you fell in love with a trick
You're pathetic to the game
You fell in love with a fucking trick
What's the trim?
You fell in love with a fucking trick. That's pathetic to me
Like I feel really bad for you that you literally fell in love with a trick
Like you fell in love with a fucking trick summer. That's pathetic. Are you gonna dragon for us? Like you fell in love with a trick
You literally fell in love with a fucking trick
Like that's sad
You fell in love with a man that loves me
Beautiful children you think
Saddled he's settled and I don't know the trick that's what that is. I fell in love with a trick
The fact that you fell in love with a trick is so prosthetic to me
You know
Like to you I mean you think that he's in love with you. No, no stay say please like you don't work back
No, I was literally a trip to lie to you and you fell in love with him back
After a trick manipulated you you fell in love with him. That's really
That's so amazing
That's really sad to me that you fell in love with a fucking trick
She cried now. She's already upset. That's pathetic to me that a trick fell in love with you and you actually believed his lies
You believe the 17 year old. Yeah, I believe his lies. 17 years old. Yes, 17 years old. Look at that, look at that.
He's waiting for you're gone. A trick fell in love with you and you actually think he actually loves you fully.
A trick. I'm all men. A trick.
I mean, yeah, I mean, it's like Fliria, you just keep repeating the same thing you want to talk about something else. I mean, you just keep saying it's trick it's trick it's trick. I mean, it's like it's becoming it's becoming old at this point.
Fliria, do you want to talk about something else or are you she's crushed up great. She's been crying. That was he keeps repeating her though like
And a day summer I could never fall in love with someone that started paying me from the beginning I
Can never I never fall in love with someone that actually was paying me, you know
But that is he was paying you and you actually fell in love with him after he's been paying you this whole time
I could never, I could never, after someone's been paying you for so long for you to believe
the manipulation of someone paying me, I guess he does pay all the bills and pay the mortgage
payment and the car payments and so, I'm not really sad, I'm not really sad.
That's a marriage. That's a marriage, you know
The fact that someone's been paying you monthly
And you actually believe in the monthly allowance
You can literally have convinced yourself that that monthly allowance is the reason why he loves you
I feel really bad for you, you know
And it's beautiful like that monthly allowance has generally made me feel bad for you, you know that okay
You know
She's a for a guy that's going to give you put your gear at least a little bit of money to play with every literally a whole monthly
Allowance has literally convinced you so bad for 17 years
So flirty you're all about love
You're all about love all you're looking for is love. You don't care about I just feel so bad for you that a monthly allowance summer
Everything actually
Yeah, 17 years of a monthly allowance has convinced you. I'm so sorry for you actually
18 years of a monthly allowance has made you convince so bad. I feel really bad for you
Eighteen years of a marriage has convinced you
But she's totally crashing I generally feel bad for you
Years of your bills, you think he just loves you
In that light with your
Literally paying your bills for 18 years and you think he loves you actually
I feel really bad for you.
18 years of him paying for you.
That's really pathetic to me.
Okay.
Are you going to say something original?
You just go on the first it was like, oh, you know your husband
He fell in love with your trick and then it's like oh monthly allowance. I was 18 years. I I mean, I don't know what's what almost happening
Okay
Monthly allowances and you think
That's really sad to me
That's really sad to me, 18 years, 18 years, 18 years, shut up,
cycle. You're a fucking rapist, Alex. I'm not even screaming.
There's nobody brave enough to come up here with these two
lunatics besides me. Do you understand? I'm not even young,
though. I'm on to one of these motherfuckers drop. No one's
coming up because no one's brave enough.
You got to be a 10-star general come up you a Florian summer
For heaven's hair is sticking out like the exorcist and she keeps
Repeating the same things over and over for her. Yeah, are you okay? What's going on?
You're a rapist Alex. You're a fucking rape
That's lander by the way
I saw you tell me go or whatever you name is it like
I'll be back